<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on MuayData blog</title>
    <link>/categories/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on MuayData blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a rel=&#34;license noopener&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC-ND 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ONE Featherweight Kickboxing World GP:
Petrosyan vs Petchmorakot</title>
      <link>/post/onefc-wc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/onefc-wc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last Friday, ONE-fc come out with one of the biggest and most anticipated shows in the history of the sport, with 8 among the best kickboxers in the World battling for the Featherweight Kicknboxing Grand Prix belt and the prize of &lt;em&gt;one million dollars&lt;/em&gt;! One of the favorites, Giorgio &amp;ldquo;the Doctor&amp;rdquo; Petrosyan lost against the 2 division Lumpinee Stadium champion Petchmorakot Pechindee Accademy and, as often happens for split decisions, the result generated some frustation among the fan base. &lt;em&gt;Who landed more stikes and how tight was the fight?&lt;/em&gt;. I carefully looked at the video of the fight in slowmotion, patiently scored each single strike using a profession (event logging software)[&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.boris.unito.it/&#34;&gt;https://www.boris.unito.it/&lt;/a&gt;] and come out with &lt;em&gt;few charts of stats to answer those questions&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snakes, pandas, sea born creatures and how to find them</title>
      <link>/post/reticulate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/reticulate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s the fastest way to read a csv file in &lt;code&gt;R&lt;/code&gt;? Among the &lt;code&gt;R&lt;/code&gt; packages, the ultra-fast sprinter is certainly &lt;code&gt;data.table&lt;/code&gt; but&amp;hellip;few years ago, the introduction of the package &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.rstudio.com/2018/03/26/reticulate-r-interface-to-python/&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;reticulate&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; gave us the possibility of use &lt;code&gt;python&lt;/code&gt; and in particular the library &lt;code&gt;pandas&lt;/code&gt; to read files in &lt;code&gt;R&lt;/code&gt;. Would &lt;code&gt;pandas&lt;/code&gt; (used in &lt;code&gt;R&lt;/code&gt;) be faster than &lt;code&gt;data.table&lt;/code&gt;? How would its performance compare with &lt;code&gt;readr&lt;/code&gt; or base &lt;code&gt;R&lt;/code&gt;? Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do not invoke me</title>
      <link>/post/do-not-invoke-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/do-not-invoke-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You know how to apply a function to a list of elements (&lt;code&gt;apply&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;purrr:map&lt;/code&gt;) but&amp;hellip; do you know how to apply a &lt;strong&gt;list of functions&lt;/strong&gt; to the &lt;strong&gt;same data/arguments&lt;/strong&gt;? In this short post we will answer that question.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fighting Diseases with Predictive Modeling</title>
      <link>/post/fighting-diseases/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/fighting-diseases/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this post we will analyze the data of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www .cpc.unc.edu/projects/addhealth/about&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ADD HEALTH&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a national longitudinal study that enrolled  ~90000 adolescents and followed them up for 20 years. Using the &lt;em&gt;R&lt;/em&gt; package &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/topepo/caret&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;caret&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, we will train and evaluate different models (regression, decision tree, random Forest) in order to predict drug use behavior in adulthood from information (friends, social activities, parents and others) collected during adolescence. This will give us the opportunity to play and get familiarized with the most important &lt;code&gt;caret&lt;/code&gt; functions as well as to introduce seminal concepts of machine learning.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animated Prison</title>
      <link>/post/animated-prison/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/animated-prison/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this post we will get the datasets and write the code to create the following visualization of the rate of incarceration over time in U.S (custody and jurisdiction counts of all prisoners).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;[Double click for full screen]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe title=&#34;Prison_video&#34; height=&#34;400&#34; src=&#34;/data_post3/output.mp4&#34; frameBorder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Il Re di Twitter? (PART II)</title>
      <link>/post/re-di-twitter-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/re-di-twitter-ii/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In questa seconda parte analizzeremo il contenuto dei tweets di Di Maio, Salvini e Martina e scopriremo quante volte e quando particolari parole sono state utilizzate dai 3 politici. Per finire andremo a vedere se alcune di queste parole sono associate ad un alto numero di like.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Il Re di Twitter? (PARTE I)</title>
      <link>/post/re-di-twitter-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/re-di-twitter-i/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In questa serie di Posts andremo ad analizzare gli ultimi 3200 tweets di Di Maio, Salvini e Martina. Il mio studio sarà diviso in 2 parti:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nella &lt;strong&gt;parte I&lt;/strong&gt; analizzeremo le abitudini dei 3 leader e  scopriremo chi dei 3 è il più attivo, quando durante la giornata, quanto sono popolari i vari tweets e molte altre informazioni.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nella &lt;strong&gt;parte II&lt;/strong&gt; ci addentreremo nel contenuto dei tweets e andremo a vedere quali sono le parole e i lemmi più usati dai 3 politici.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>