<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MuayData blog</title>
    <link>https://muaydata.netlify.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MuayData blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a rel=&#34;license noopener&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC-ND 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://muaydata.netlify.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://muaydata.netlify.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muaydata.netlify.com/about/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://muaydata.netlify.com/data/other/image_cover.png&#34; alt=&#34;cover&#34; width=&#34;600px&#34; hight=&#34;400px&#34; style=&#34;display: block; margin: auto;&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a data analysis enthusiast and fan of the art of the eight limbs (Muay Thai). I was born and I grow up in the eternal city. Now I live in the city of the late Edgar Allan Poe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog I will publish analysis of muay-thai and kickboxing fights. Why do I do that? Well, even when I watch fights I cannot avoid to think about numbers!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you like &lt;code&gt;R&lt;/code&gt; check &lt;a href=&#34;https://rden.netlify.com/&#34;&gt;my other blog&lt;/a&gt; that focuses on programming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog was built in &lt;code&gt;RStudio&lt;/code&gt; using &lt;code&gt;RMarkdown&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;Rblogdown&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;Hugo&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The best lightweight kickboxers by the numbers</title>
      <link>https://muaydata.netlify.com/post/lightweight-ranking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muaydata.netlify.com/post/lightweight-ranking/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;How well do you know the best 5 lightweight kickboxers in the world? Do you know who is the tallest? &amp;hellip;or the oldest? Who would you say is the scariest in terms of knock-out power? Let&amp;rsquo;s check it out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who are the best?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/br&gt;
This June, the lightweight kickboxing ranking by &lt;a href=&#34;http://combatpress.com/2019/06/combat-press-kickboxing-rankings-june-2019/&#34;&gt;Combat Press&lt;/a&gt; was the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marat Grigorian&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sitthichai Sitsongpeenong&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Superbon Banchamek&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Giorgio Petrosyan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chingiz Allazov&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tayfun Ozcan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Endy Semeleer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jonay Risco&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Samy Sana&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yodsanklai Fairtex&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s compare the data of the top 5 fighters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the charts, fighters will be arranged from left to right by their ranking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;height-and-age&#34;&gt;Height and Age&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tallest fighter is Allazov (5 ft 11 in), whereas the shortest is Sitthichai (5 ft 8 &lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; in). &lt;strong&gt;The top 2 ranked fighters are also the shortest.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://muaydata.netlify.com/post/2019-06-16-kickboxing-lightweight-ranking_files/figure-html/height-1.png&#34; width=&#34;672&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The top 5 fighters are &lt;strong&gt;between 26 (Allazov) and 34 (Petrosyan) years old&lt;/strong&gt;. Grigorian and Sitthichai are both 28 years old (but Grigorian is few months younger).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://muaydata.netlify.com/post/2019-06-16-kickboxing-lightweight-ranking_files/figure-html/age-1.png&#34; width=&#34;672&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;wins-and-kos&#34;&gt;Wins and  KOs&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All of the top 5 kickboxers have phenomenal records, with ~75% (Superbon) to ~95% (Petrosyan and Allazov) of victories&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://muaydata.netlify.com/post/2019-06-16-kickboxing-lightweight-ranking_files/figure-html/perc_win-1.png&#34; width=&#34;672&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Petrosyan and Allazov are close to perfection&lt;/strong&gt; with about 19 victories every 20 fights. Let&amp;rsquo;s suppose that we toss a  coin 4 times and we get every single time head&amp;hellip; Would you bet on that? Well, for those 2 fighters, the probability of &lt;strong&gt;not winning a fight&lt;/strong&gt; is very close to that (actually a little bit less for Petrosyan)&amp;hellip;we can say that is extremely unlikely!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who is more likely to end up a fight with a KO win?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://muaydata.netlify.com/post/2019-06-16-kickboxing-lightweight-ranking_files/figure-html/KO_wins-1.png&#34; width=&#34;672&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The KO machine is Allazov&lt;/strong&gt;. He finished &lt;strong&gt;more than half of his fights with his opponent lying on the canvas&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Petrosyan and Grigorian have impressive KO power:&lt;/strong&gt; about ~45% of their fights ending with a win by KO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 2 Thai fighters, &lt;strong&gt;Sitthichai and Superbon&lt;/strong&gt; have the &lt;strong&gt;lowest percent of KOs victories&lt;/strong&gt; but on the other hand also the highest number of fights (159 and 143, respectively).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;winning-streak&#34;&gt;Winning Streak&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Among the 5 top kickboxer, &lt;strong&gt;Petrosyan has the longest winning streak (14) and has not lost or draw a fight since 2013&lt;/strong&gt; (against Andy Ristie).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Superbon is currently in 8 winning streak&lt;/strong&gt;. His last defeat was in a fight against the number 1 Grigorian and came by a tremendous KO stoppage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grigorian, Sitthichai, Allazov, they have all recently lost a fight in bouts against each other or Petrosyan&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://muaydata.netlify.com/post/2019-06-16-kickboxing-lightweight-ranking_files/figure-html/curr_streak-1.png&#34; width=&#34;672&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary-and-table&#34;&gt;Summary and Table&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here some few facts about the top 5 lightweight kickboxers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The taller fighter is Allazov. The 2 shortest fighters, Grigorian and Sitthichai are also the top 2 in the current ranking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Petrosyan is the oldest fighter (34) whereas Allazov the youngest (26).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With 95% of their fight won, Petrosyan and Allazov have the highest percentage of victories (the others are all above 75%).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allazov is the KO machine with more than half of his fights finished by KO. Grigorian and Petrosyan have ~45%, whereas  Sitthichai and Superbon ~20% of their fights won by KO.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Petrosyan is currently in a 14-fight winning streak.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check the table below if you want to make more comparisons by your own! &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;scroll to the left to see all the columns and the arrows to order them&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe seamless src=&#34;https://muaydata.netlify.com/data/data_post3/d1.html&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;400&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buonanotte e buone botte.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;all the data was scraped from en.wikipedia&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ONE World GP quarter-final: time in break</title>
      <link>https://muaydata.netlify.com/post/one-world-gp-quarter-final-breaks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muaydata.netlify.com/post/one-world-gp-quarter-final-breaks/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After an official review, the bout between &lt;strong&gt;Petchmorakot versus Petroysan&lt;/strong&gt; was overturn to a &amp;ldquo;No Contest&amp;rdquo; because &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/yodchatri/posts/2345566252172189&#34;&gt;illegal clinching was not adequately controlled by the referee&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;How much time was wasted&lt;/strong&gt; because the referee had to repeatedly break the fighters during clinch?&lt;/br&gt;
..and &lt;strong&gt;how does that compare with&lt;/strong&gt; the time in break of &lt;strong&gt;the other quarter-final fights?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/br&gt;
We will answer those questions using few charts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-tale-of-the-numbers&#34;&gt;The tale of the numbers&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;time-in-break-by-round&#34;&gt;Time in break by round&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last month ONE Championship put out an amazing fight card with 8 among the best kickboxers in the world battling for the kickboxing featherweight belt and the 1 million dollar prize. The event delivered some  breathtaking action but also one of the biggest controversy in the recent kickboxing history: &lt;strong&gt;Petchmorakot versus Petroysan&lt;/strong&gt; was overturn to a &amp;ldquo;No Contest&amp;rdquo; because of the illegal clinching by Petchmorakot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why was the clinching by Petchmorakot considered illegal? In a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/yodchatri/posts/2350703531658461&#34;&gt;facebook post&lt;/a&gt;, the ONE Championship CEO Chatri Sityodtong explained that [clinch]&amp;hellip;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;is not allowed for stalling, tying up an opponent, or holding. It is also not allowed directly after an attack as a defensive technique. Under ONE rules, the clinch is ONLY allowed for offensive aggression with strikes&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://lawrencekenshin.com/&#34;&gt;Lawrence Kenshin&lt;/a&gt; expended on that with an in-dept video analysis and breakdown of the fight. Here is an extract of the video in which he explains some of the key concepts behind the &amp;ldquo;No Contest&amp;rdquo; decision (make sure to check the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=80NDxqWfeys&#34;&gt;full video&lt;/a&gt; of Lawrence Kenshin):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://muaydata.netlify.com/data/data_post2/Picture1.png&#34; alt=&#34;Kenshin&#34; width=&#34;500px&#34; height=&#34;500px&#34; style=&#34;display: block; margin: auto;&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words, kickboxing is all about &lt;strong&gt;continuing striking action&lt;/strong&gt;, and thus fighters are expected to &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;transition out of clinch without referee&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;. When the fighters engage in clinch and hold after, they force the referee to step in and break them, &lt;strong&gt;taking away a lot of time from the real action&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How much time was taken away from the action by the referee breaks?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;I analyzed all the four fights and recorded the time in break&lt;/strong&gt; (time from the referee saying &amp;ldquo;Stop&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;Go&amp;rdquo;). I did not include breaks resulting from knock downs or cut kicks that are normal part of an &amp;ldquo;healthy&amp;rdquo; striking action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following chart shows for each round (in the x axis),  the percent of  time (y axis) spent in break. Data of each of the fights is displayed in a different colored column.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Click on the figure to enlarge it&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://muaydata.netlify.com/post/2019-06-06-onefc_wc_breaks_files/figure-html/tot-1.png&#34; width=&#34;672&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In round1, action was mostly continuous in all of the 4 fights&lt;/strong&gt; and time in break was not more than 10% of the round time (Askerov-Kehel: 18 sec). Petchmorakot-Petrosyan were in break for about 5% of the round (10 sec that included the low blow by Petrosyan),
whereas Yodsanklay-Sana and Nattawut-Moisa gave us a round of unstopped (or almost unstopped)  action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In round2, time in break went up in all the fights, but to an alarming level in Petchmorakot-Petrosyan&lt;/strong&gt;. Askerov-Kehel, Yodsanklai-Sana and Nattawut-Moisa spent ~20%, 13% and 3% of round2 in break, respectively. On the other hand, &lt;strong&gt;Petchmorakot-Petrosyan had almost 30% of round2  in break&amp;hellip;52 sec of the 180 sec of the round not fighting!&lt;/strong&gt; Noteworthy, the measure that I am reporting here is the time in which action is &lt;em&gt;not allowed&lt;/em&gt; (the referee said &amp;ldquo;Stop&amp;rdquo;), and so does not include other inactive periods (in clinch or outside) in which action is permitted but fighters do not engage. In other words, the current measure is quite conservative and presumably is an underestimate of  the inactive time of the fight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why did break time increase of 5 fold (from 10 to 52 sec) in round2 of Petchmorakot-Petrosyan fight? &lt;/br&gt;
Well, we know that &lt;strong&gt;this was part of (or a collateral effect) of Petchmorakot&amp;rsquo;s strategy for landing knees&lt;/strong&gt;. In a post-fight interview Petchmorakot said:
&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;I changed my strategy going into the second round. My manager, Mr. Nuttadaj, told me to use my reach, jab my way in, and land the left long knee&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He also added: &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Going into the third, I stuck with that game plan, and it worked.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And indeed &lt;strong&gt;Petchmorakot stuck with his strategy and time in break remain quite stable in round3 (~27%, 49 sec)&lt;/strong&gt;. Also in Askerov-Kehel and Yodsanklay-Sana fights the time in break did not change considerably and remain under or equal to 18% of the round time (≤34 sec). There was no break due to holding in Nattawut-Moisa round3 but in that round Moisa was knock down twice and then TKO at 1&amp;rsquo;36&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;total-time-in-break&#34;&gt;Total time in break&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In total, &lt;strong&gt;Petchmorakot-Petrosyan spent 111 sec of the fight in break&lt;/strong&gt; (that is dangerously close to 2 minutes of no fight). How does that compare with the totals of the other fights?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;table&gt;
&lt;caption&gt;Table 1: Total time in Break&lt;/caption&gt;
 &lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;border-bottom:hidden&#34; colspan=&#34;1&#34;&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;border-bottom:hidden&#34; colspan=&#34;1&#34;&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;border-bottom:hidden; padding-bottom:0; padding-left:3px;padding-right:3px;text-align: center; &#34; colspan=&#34;2&#34;&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;border-bottom: 1px solid #ddd; padding-bottom: 5px; &#34;&gt;Relative to Petchmorakot-Petrosyan&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
   &lt;th style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt; Fight &lt;/th&gt;
   &lt;th style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; sec &lt;/th&gt;
   &lt;th style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; sec &lt;/th&gt;
   &lt;th style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt; percent &lt;/th&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt; Askerov-Kehel &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; 87 &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; -24 &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt; -27% &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt; Yodsanklai-Sana &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; 58 &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; -53 &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt; -92% &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt; Nattawut-Moisa &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; 9 &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; -102 &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt; -1104% &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;
Among the 4 fights of the quarter final, &lt;strong&gt;Petchmorakot-Petrosyan was the fight with most time in break&lt;/strong&gt;, followed by Askerov-Kehel (87 sec), Yodsanklai-Sana (58 sec) and  Nattawut-Moisa (9 sec; &lt;strong&gt;table above&lt;/strong&gt;). Askerov-Kehel spent ~24 sec (~27%) less in break  than Petchmorakot-Petrosyan. &lt;/br&gt;
Is this difference of time in break between Petchmorakot-Petrosyan and Askerov-Kehel big enough to justify alone the overturn of one of the fight but not the other? There are a couple of considerations that need to be made to answer that question. &lt;strong&gt;1) Petchmorakot-Petrosyan overturn was also motivated by the fact that, of the 2 fighters only one was almost exclusively responsible for the holding and defensive clinch&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;Lawrance Kenshin&lt;/strong&gt; argued in &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=80NDxqWfeys&#34;&gt;his analysis&lt;/a&gt; that there was &lt;strong&gt;enough ground for deducting multiple points to Petchmorakot&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;2) When put it in prospective, the difference of time in break between Petchmorakot-Petrosyan and Askerov-Kehel is not trivial&lt;/strong&gt;. Petchmorakot-Petrosyan spent 24 sec more in break than Askerov-Kehel. That is equivalent of having &lt;strong&gt;3 separate 8-counts more of inactivity in in Petchmorakot-Petrosyanthan fight than in Askerov-Kehel (i.e. on the top of 87 seconds)&lt;/strong&gt; but&amp;hellip; without even a knock down. Just few days ago we were reminded that 8 seconds can be enough to get back on your feet after a knock down and  punch your way to a win (i.e. Joshua-Ruiz!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;single-breaks&#34;&gt;Single breaks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why did Petchmorakot-Petrosyan spent more time in break than the other fighters? Were the breaks more numerous or were they longer than in  the other of the quarter-final fights?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well a little bit of both.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Click on the figure to enlarge it&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://muaydata.netlify.com/post/2019-06-06-onefc_wc_breaks_files/figure-html/jitter-1.png&#34; width=&#34;672&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the chart above, each point represents a break. The length of the break  is indicated on the y axis on the left, the fight where the break was observed is reported on the x-axis on the bottom. Again,  we have different colors associated to different fights. The more the points are high, the more the breaks are long. If you see many points of the same color, then that means that there were many breaks in that fight! As you can see, &lt;strong&gt;there were numerous breaks in Petchmorakot-Petrosyan but also in Askerov-Kehel&lt;/strong&gt; (where Onari was a referee too). The problem is that &lt;strong&gt;the breaks in Petchmorakot-Petrosyan fight tended to be longer than in the other fights!&lt;/strong&gt; There are 5 breaks that lasted between 6 to ~7 seconds in Petchmorakot-Petrosyan, but only one that is that long in Askerov-Kehel fight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why did it took so long? For 2 reasons. In some of those breaks the referee talked to Petchmorakot, and that took extra time away from action. In others, the referee had to physically separate the fighters, a process that eats up time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Petchmorakot-Petrosyan spent more time in break than any of the quarter-final fights. A total of  ~111 seconds of that fight were spent actually&amp;hellip;not fighting&lt;/strong&gt; (break time), with most of this inactive time in round2 (52 sec, 29% of round time) and round3 (49 sec, ~27).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The breaks in Petchmorakot-Petrosyan  were numerous but also tended to last more than in the other fights&lt;/strong&gt;. This was due to the extra time needed by the referee to talk to Petchmorakot and/or to actively separate the 2 fighters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And so? I enjoyed the fight and I was not that excited for kickboxing tournament since the time of the old K1 of Masato, Buakaw and Souwer. I think that Petchmorakot is an extremely dangerous fighter also under kickboxing rules and he showed it to us by landing some heavy punches and quite scary knees. So&amp;hellip;I just hope that there will be soon a rematch!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;edit-july-6&#34;&gt;EDIT: July 6.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;and ** a rematch has been confirmed**&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;blockquote class=&#34;instagram-media&#34; data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/p/ByaUdD4B1-F/&#34; data-instgrm-version=&#34;12&#34; style=&#34; background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);&#34;&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;padding:16px;&#34;&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/p/ByaUdD4B1-F/&#34; style=&#34; background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt; &lt;div style=&#34; display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;&#34;&gt; &lt;div style=&#34;background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&#34;display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;&#34;&gt; &lt;div style=&#34; background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&#34; background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;padding: 19% 0;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&#34;display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;&#34;&gt;&lt;svg width=&#34;50px&#34; height=&#34;50px&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 60 60&#34; version=&#34;1.1&#34; xmlns=&#34;https://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34; xmlns:xlink=&#34;https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink&#34;&gt;&lt;g stroke=&#34;none&#34; stroke-width=&#34;1&#34; fill=&#34;none&#34; fill-rule=&#34;evenodd&#34;&gt;&lt;g transform=&#34;translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)&#34; fill=&#34;#000000&#34;&gt;&lt;g&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;padding-top: 8px;&#34;&gt; &lt;div style=&#34; color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;&#34;&gt; View this post on Instagram&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;padding: 12.5% 0;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&#34;display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;div style=&#34;background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&#34;background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&#34;background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;margin-left: 8px;&#34;&gt; &lt;div style=&#34; background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&#34; width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;margin-left: auto;&#34;&gt; &lt;div style=&#34; width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&#34; background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&#34; width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p style=&#34; margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;&#34;&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/p/ByaUdD4B1-F/&#34; style=&#34; color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Rematch between @petchmorakot.official and @giorgiopetrosyan is confirmed. They are fighting on 12 July in Kuala Lumpur 💥💥 @yindeeman posted this on his personal facebook, &amp;#34;The hardest decision ever in life!!! It was two weeks that I was very stressed about the situation that occurred between ONECHAMPIONSHIP and PETCHYINDEE over the fight of Petchmorakot vs Petrosyan. After the competition end, a lot of Petrosyan fans came to our social media channels such as Facebook page and Instagram. Most of them said we were cheating, we stole their victory. At first we tried to understand them as they might still in shocked that their idol was unbelievably defeated.  Nevertheless after ONE CHAMPIONSHIP announced the rematch of Petchmorakot with Petrosyan, I was truly in shocked and I don’t think this is a fair decision. Thus, as you all known Petchmorakot had announced to withdrawn himself from the competition. The situation had become worse as once Petrosayn’s fans knew that we had withdrawn, they all came to say that we are coward or we were afraid to fight with Petrosyan even the victory that we get were came from cheating.  Petchmorakot who was ordained as a monk had called me to give him a chance to fight for his honor and to prove to everyone that he deserve the victory. Until two days ago, I received a call from Khun Chatri about the solution of this issue. ONE CHAMPIONSHIP apologized for the incident and explains to me about the Kickboxing rules which lead to a lot of misunderstanding between the fight, in this point to REMATCH is the best option for both of them. For Petchmorakot, Khun Chatri proposed 1 million baht for his fighting fee along with giving him the opportunity to fight in WORLD GRAND PRIX which is in Muay Thai rule with the price of 1 million dollars no matter how the result of this match will be. ONE CHAMPIONSHIP confirmed that this rematch will be fair to both sides and the judgment of this rematch will be final. Then I asked Pra Petchmorakot for his decision while I ready to give him all money without any deduction no matter the result is, in return of his hard work and to encourage him to the victory. (Continue in comment)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style=&#34; color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;&#34;&gt;A post shared by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/petchyindee/&#34; style=&#34; color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px;&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt; THE MASTER OF MUAYTHAI 👊&lt;/a&gt; (@petchyindee) on &lt;time style=&#34; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;&#34; datetime=&#34;2019-06-07T14:04:56+00:00&#34;&gt;Jun 7, 2019 at 7:04am PDT&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async src=&#34;//www.instagram.com/embed.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ONE World GP: Petchmorakot vs Petrosyan</title>
      <link>https://muaydata.netlify.com/post/onefc-wc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muaydata.netlify.com/post/onefc-wc/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Last Friday, &lt;strong&gt;Petchmorakot Pechindee Academy&lt;/strong&gt; brought home a stunning win against  &lt;strong&gt;Giorgio &amp;ldquo;the Doctor&amp;rdquo; Petrosyan&lt;/strong&gt; and, as often happens with split decisions, the judges score generated a lot of discussion.
The decision was later declared &lt;strong&gt;No Contest&lt;/strong&gt; because of the inadequate control by the referee of excessive clinching. &lt;strong&gt;I carefully looked at the video of the fight, patiently recorded each single strike to come out with few charts of stats&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- https://discourse.gohugo.io/t/solved-add-line-break-in-yaml-file/13446/2 --&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-tale-of-the-numbers&#34;&gt;The tale of the numbers&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;count-by-class-and-round&#34;&gt;Count by class and round&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The much anticipated &lt;strong&gt;ONE Featherweight Kickboxing Grand Prix&lt;/strong&gt; met the fan expectations with a show that  kept us on the edge of the seat, delivered memorable knock downs and unanticipated turn of events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The underdog, Petchmorakot Pechindee Accademy got an unexpected win, under kickboxing rules, against arguably the best pound-for-pound kickboxer of all times, Giorgio Petrosyan. The 2 division Lumpinee Stadium World Championships &lt;strong&gt;Petchmorakot  Pechindee Accademy&lt;/strong&gt; is certainly not a rookie of the game, but under these tournament rules he could not use some of his most sharp weapons (elbows)&amp;hellip;nevertheless he managed to keep up with Giorgio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today (Wednesday, May 22), Chatri Sityodtong announced on Facebook that &lt;em&gt;a Competition Committee declared the bout a No Contest&lt;/em&gt;: Petchmorakot  Pechindee Accademy relied too heavily on clinch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I looked at the fight in slow-motion and, using a profession &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.boris.unito.it/&#34;&gt;event logging software&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;I recorded all the strikes annotating those that landed&lt;/strong&gt;. I intentionally avoided to include any metric of the &amp;ldquo;intensity&amp;rdquo; of the strikes which would have required a much more subjective and thus opinable evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, let&amp;rsquo;s cut to the chase and get to the first chart: &lt;strong&gt;strikes landed&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Click on the figure to enlarge it&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://muaydata.netlify.com/post/2019-05-20-onefc-wc_files/figure-html/likert-1.png&#34; width=&#34;672&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;first round was all about Petrosyan&lt;/strong&gt;. He outboxed Petchmorakot (11 punches landed), he was successful with low and front kicks (8 kicks landed) and he also landed a couple of knees.  &lt;strong&gt;Pechmorakot&lt;/strong&gt; had really few answers. Most observators (Petchmorakot too!) agree that this was Petrosyan&amp;rsquo;s round.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the &lt;strong&gt;second round, Pechmorakot&lt;/strong&gt; come back with a strategy: &lt;strong&gt;jab his way in, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.onefc.com/articles/emotional-petchmorakot-reveals-how-he-beat-petrosyan/&#34;&gt;clinch and land knees&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. This strategy payed and &lt;strong&gt;Petchmorakot&lt;/strong&gt; landed many knees (19) and also occasional punches (4). &lt;strong&gt;Petrosyan relied less on kicks but continued to score  with his boxing&lt;/strong&gt; (14 punches). He also managed to land some knees in the clinch too. In terms of number of strikes landed (see also table below), &lt;strong&gt;this was a very very close round&lt;/strong&gt; (I counted 24 for Petchmorakot and 25 for Petrosyan).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;third round was the consolidation of Pechmorakot&amp;rsquo;s strategy&lt;/strong&gt;. He continued to enter into clinch to knee (10 knees) and effectively nullifying Petrosyan&amp;rsquo;s attempt of boxing. This was the round in which &lt;strong&gt;Petrosyan landed the least number of strikes&lt;/strong&gt;. In this round &lt;strong&gt;Petchmorakot got a slight edge over  Petroysian in terms of strikes landed&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;tabulated-totals-by-round&#34;&gt;Tabulated totals by round&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can have an even simpler &lt;strong&gt;bare-bone picture of the fight&lt;/strong&gt; looking at the &lt;strong&gt;strikes landed vs total&lt;/strong&gt; (landed + thrown; table below).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
 &lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;border-bottom:hidden&#34; colspan=&#34;1&#34;&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;border-bottom:hidden; padding-bottom:0; padding-left:3px;padding-right:3px;text-align: center; &#34; colspan=&#34;2&#34;&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;border-bottom: 1px solid #ddd; padding-bottom: 5px; &#34;&gt;Landed&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;border-bottom:hidden; padding-bottom:0; padding-left:3px;padding-right:3px;text-align: center; &#34; colspan=&#34;2&#34;&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;border-bottom: 1px solid #ddd; padding-bottom: 5px; &#34;&gt;Total&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
   &lt;th style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt; round &lt;/th&gt;
   &lt;th style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; Petchmorakot &lt;/th&gt;
   &lt;th style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; Petrosyan &lt;/th&gt;
   &lt;th style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; Petchmorakot &lt;/th&gt;
   &lt;th style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; Petrosyan &lt;/th&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt; 1 &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; 7 &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; 21 &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; 65 &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; 70 &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt; 2 &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; 24 &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; 25 &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; 78 &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; 64 &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt; 3 &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; 11 &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; 8 &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; 59 &lt;/td&gt;
   &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right;&#34;&gt; 43 &lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the &lt;strong&gt;first round Petrosyan landed about 3-times more strikes than Pechmorakot&lt;/strong&gt;. In the &lt;strong&gt;second round, the number of strikes landed by the 2 fighters was quite close&lt;/strong&gt; (24 vs 25), whereas &lt;strong&gt;in the third, Petchmorakot had a slight edge over Petrosyan&lt;/strong&gt; (11 vs 8). In terms of strikes thrown, &lt;strong&gt;both the fighters were similarly active&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have to admit that these numbers surprised me: I had the impression that &lt;strong&gt;Petrosyan&lt;/strong&gt; was much more active than &lt;strong&gt;Petchmorakot&lt;/strong&gt;. So I decided to look back at the fight, check more metrics and then I got it&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;lead-and-back-side&#34;&gt;Lead and Back side&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s look at the total shots and distinguish them depending on the side used to strikes.
In the following plot the lead side strikes are plotted on the right side of the polygon while the back side strikes on the left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://muaydata.netlify.com/post/2019-05-20-onefc-wc_files/g134.png&#34; alt=&#34;radar&#34; width=&#34;500px&#34; height=&#34;500px&#34; style=&#34;display: block; margin: auto;&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Petrosyan extensively used his boxing throwing both his left and power hand in similar proportions&lt;/strong&gt;. He usually avoid to throw bare single shots and prefers to rely more on strike combinations, in this fight jab-cross-hook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Petchmorak&lt;/strong&gt; used extensively his lead head that throw more than 100 times. How many of these lead hands did he successfully land? Only 6 times in all the fight (data not shown). While this seems a quite
unsuccessful use of a technique, it was just part of the strategy: Petchmorak &lt;strong&gt;used his left hand to disrupt Petrosyan boxing, enter in to clinch, and to land knees&lt;/strong&gt;. He literally throw more than 105 jabs in order to land 33 knees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I counted each single strike and&amp;hellip; &lt;strong&gt;it still was a really tight fight!&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Petrosyan&lt;/strong&gt; clearly dominated in the first round and landed 3-times more strikes than &lt;strong&gt;Petchmorakot&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the second round &lt;strong&gt;Petchmorakot&lt;/strong&gt; started &lt;strong&gt;clinching&lt;/strong&gt; and landed several knees: overall the number of strikes landed by the 2 fighters was virtually the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the last round &lt;strong&gt;Petchmorakot&lt;/strong&gt; kept kneeing while &lt;strong&gt;Petrosyan&lt;/strong&gt; landed fewer punches than in the previous rounds: in these last round &lt;strong&gt;Petchmorakot&lt;/strong&gt; landed few more strikes than &lt;strong&gt;Petrosyan&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In summary, &lt;strong&gt;if we look at the strikes landed, it could have gone one way or the other, and thus the decision mostly depends on the damage and &amp;ldquo;cleanness&amp;rdquo; that you attribute to the shots&lt;/strong&gt;. Do you think that Petchmorakot&amp;rsquo;s knees made more damage than Petrosyan&amp;rsquo;s punches or viceversa?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bout has been declared a No Contest &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/yodchatri/posts/2345566252172189&#34;&gt;see link&lt;/a&gt;&amp;hellip;so we are ready and excited for the next battle of these 2 fighters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;did-you-see-this&#34;&gt;Did you see this?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A couple of actions that you might have overlooked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Petrosyan Upper-Hook&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe title=&#34;petrosyan&#34; height=&#34;400&#34; src=&#34;https://muaydata.netlify.com/data/data_post1/petrosyan.mp4&#34; frameBorder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Petchmorakot Overhand&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;iframe title=&#34;petrosyan&#34; height=&#34;400&#34; src=&#34;https://muaydata.netlify.com/data/data_post1/petch.mp4&#34; frameBorder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>